Unchanged-1
Unchanged-2
Unchanged-3
Same start case 1, same text
Same start case 1, text 1
Same start case 1, text 2
Same start case 2, same text
Same start case 2, text 1
Same start case 2, text 2
Same start case 3, same text
Same start case 3, text 1
Same start case 3, text 2
Start before case 1, same text
Start before case 1, text 1
Start before case 1, text 2
Start before case 2, same text
Start before case 2, text 1
Start before case 2, text 2
Start before case 3, same text
Start before case 3, text 1
Start before case 3, text 2
Start after end before, same text
Start after end before, text 1
Start after end before, text 2
Start after with overlap, same text
Start after with overlap, text 1
Start after with overlap, text 2
Start after and outreach, same text
Start after and outreach, text 1
Start after and outreach, text 2
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
short duration
(hello world)
[hello world]
hello world
hello world TEXT-SKIP hello world
goodbye...